{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The lines used to create the auxiliary view should appear as ________ in the finished view.", "opta": "Object lines", "optb": "Construction lines", "optc": "Reference lines", "optd": "Construction lines", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The offset distance for the width (front to back) distance of the auxiliary view is the same distance of the ________ in the top view.", "opta": "Width", "optb": "height", "optc": "length", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The principle reason for using an auxiliary view is ________.", "opta": "to eliminate hidden lines", "optb": "to create a true projection plane from an inclined plane in one of the primary views", "optc": "to show cylinders as ellipses", "optd": "to locate center marks", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Circular shapes appear in this fashion when viewed at an angle other than 90 degrees:", "opta": "Circular", "optb": "Elliptical", "optc": "Lengthened", "optd": "Angular", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When adding dimensions to an auxiliary view it will be necessary to use the ________ tool.", "opta": "Linear dimension", "optb": "Aligned dimension", "optc": "Baseline dimension", "optd": "Angle dimension", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An efficient method for trimming the corners on an auxiliary view is to use the ________.", "opta": "0 radius fillet", "optb": "Hatch tool", "optc": "Extend tool", "optd": "Grips function", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In this type of auxiliary view, a break line is used to indicate the imaginary break in the views:", "opta": "Primary", "optb": "Secondary", "optc": "Revolved", "optd": "Partial", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When using the descriptive geometry method to create an auxiliary view the drafter should ________.", "opta": "rotate the snap grid to the same angle of the inclined plane", "optb": "offset the right vertical line of the front view", "optc": "rotate the top line of the front view 45 degrees", "optd": "offset the top line of the front view 2 inches", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This is the most common application for developments and intersections:", "opta": "Sheet metal construction", "optb": "Piping", "optc": "Architecture", "optd": "Mechanical engineering", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This type of auxiliary view is projected onto a plane that is perpendicular to one of the principal planes of projection:", "opta": "Primary", "optb": "Secondary", "optc": "Revolved", "optd": "Successive", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A partial auxiliary view usually shows only features on the ________ of the inclined line and not any projection of other planes.", "opta": "hidden lines", "optb": "plane", "optc": "center lines", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A partial auxiliary view is used to show only the ________ in the auxiliary view.", "opta": "projected inclined plane", "optb": "the projected top view", "optc": "the projected side view", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This type of surface may be a plane, a single curved surface, or a warped surface:", "opta": "Edge surface", "optb": "Ruled surface", "optc": "Auxiliary surface", "optd": "Developed surface", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In this type of view, the cutting plane line indicates both the location of the cutting plane and the direction of sight:", "opta": "Removed section", "optb": "Revolved section", "optc": "Auxiliary section", "optd": "Partial section", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The principle views associated with orthographic projection are ________.", "opta": "Front view", "optb": "Right side view", "optc": "Top view", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A secondary auxiliary view is a projection off of the ________.", "opta": "Front view", "optb": "Top view", "optc": "Primary auxiliary view", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This type of solid is formed by sweeping a shape along a linear path:", "opta": "Planar solid", "optb": "Revolved solid", "optc": "Warped solid", "optd": "Extruded solid", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}